Lookie, another friend for you.
You all play nice now, until tomorrow.
Um, are you all right?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Let's see.
Come on, let's go.
Okay...
Please wait here a bit.
Good evening.
Y-You're...!
Argh!
How dare you?!
Gahh!
Thank you for waiting.
Now, let's go.
Y-Yes...
What's this?
Where do you think you're going?
I don't know how you got out, but—
Sorry for that.
You're safe now.
We were so scared!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
Please calm yourself, Princess Olivia.
How do... you know my name?
I'm so glad you're safe.
Olivia Arnold, the second
in line to the throne.
Um, you are...
I'm an Astral of the Arnold Army.
My name is Lily.
That was when Ray and I first met.
I need more Ray in my life.
Good morning, Ray.
Good morning, Elisa.
Everything all right?
Yes. You just seem different than usual.
Oh really?
But the same goes for you.
You think so?
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 01
The Boy Who Is the World's Strongest Sorcerer
Participates in a Large Scale Magic Battle Tournament
Regarding the other day's incident.
You're saying Evan Bernstein acted alone?
There's been no movement from
Eugenics' main forces until now,
so that is a fair assumption.
And Paratrogo, who aided him, is safely
locked away in a special prison.
Evan is...
...dead.
The Hale clan took care of the aftermath.
By the way, Lydia, how is he doing?
Oh, him?
He's doing well.
He has his school life and his friends.
I think that environment is a
good influence on him right now.
It might happen sooner
than I anticipated.
Hey, did you hear?
You mean that thing?
If it's about White, then...
What?!
No! I'm talking about the Magicks War!
Thing... thing...
Oh, the completely new team battle that
doesn't limit anything to school or year?
I heard it will take place
before the choir event.
White's thing...
Seriously.
It's three people per team, right?
I bet Al wants to enter, right?
Yeah, but if it's Wisel and me,
we'd only get in Al's way, right?
You do realize that would mean
you'd be eliminated instantly, right?
Right?
The reason he's been going somewhere
with Evi lately is...
These two broad-chested guys...
Hustle!
Muscle!
Hey.
So what'll happen, I wonder?
I mean Amelia is the new
champion of Magic Chevalier.
I don't think she's too interested.
I guess that makes sense.
She probably has no reason
to enter the competition.
Right.
My feelings...
I started reading this love story by
Luna Ether because Ray was reading it...
I would've never expected it
to pierce my soul like this.
Oh...
La sta—
Who's there?
Amelia, I'd like you to compete
in the "Magicks War" with me.
Amelia, please open up.
Amelia?!
Coming.
Amelia, will you enter
the Magicks War with... us?
It's probably that thing, right?
Indeed!
What about you, Ray?
I'm going to talk to my master
about it, but I would like to enter.
You in good form?
It's just my personal opinion,
but it's not bad.
I see.
Um, is something wrong with you, Ray?
Hey, if we're going to be a team,
shouldn't you properly explain
what's going on to Ariane?
You're right.
I should give her a proper explanation.
What are you talking about?
Ariane, I am the Iceblade Sorcerer.
Huh?
Please hold on a moment.
I'm sure I must have misheard that,
so could you please repeat that?
I am one of the seven grand sorcerers,
the Iceblade Sorcerer.
Amelia?!
Yes.
How long have you known?
Since before the Magic Chevalier, I guess.
Unfair.
That's so unfair!
I'd heard that you two
were training together.
But I never understood why
you were training with Ray.
It always bothered me!
So that's what was going on!
I'll say it again...
That's so unfair!
You got one-on-one training!
From such an amazing person!
Um, well, I'm sorry.
Ariane, so you believe me?
It certainly explains a lot of mysteries.
Ariane...
So... yes.
Then let's talk about
the past a little bit.
Hey, hey, so what are
you doing after this?
Want to go get a drink?
Why not? What about you, Lydia?
Guess it can't hurt, once in a while.
What do you say, Carla?
Yes, I'll join.
Lydia-senpai.
I need to talk to you.
That means you're coming too, then!
I'm sorry?
And that's how I'm here, now.
How horrible!
The Far East War was the first war where
magic was used in real battles...
I heard that it was the
worst war of all time.
And you were at the front lines
there from such a young age...
But that's where I met my
master and the others.
And now I'm here.
So is that the master who gave you the
title of Iceblade after the war ended?
Yes.
Overheating means I still
can't release its full power,
but I did inherit the name
and station from my master.
Ray...
I challenge you!
Wait, what?
Why are you doing this?
Amelia, this is my fate as a maiden!
Your fate as a what now?
What are the terms?
Whoever says "I yield," loses.
Understood.
We haven't had a chance since last time.
That's true.
Well...
things were a bit different then.
Amelia, will you be the referee?
Okay.
Are you sure about this though?
You ended up using your powers
with Rebecca-senpai, too.
Yes.
But this time, I won't use them.
And you think you can
beat Ariane like that?
Well, I will try.
Then, let's begin!
Ogre!
I... yield.
Did you use some kind of special magic?
No.
Just an inside code
to enhance my body.
You must be lying!
There's no way you could defeat
my Ogre with just an inside code!
There are no lies here.
So this this is the power of
one of the grand seven...
Even when you're not at
your full strength,
you completely overwhelmed me.
Ariane.
This victory was only possible because
I spotted your weakness.
My weakness?
You have lots of potential to improve!
Ariane, do you want to get stronger?
Of course!
That's the spirit.
Well then, Ariane Algren!
I'll assign you an Ainsworth-style
bootcamp special regimen!
That sounds excellent!
Th-This can't be real!
B-But since I finished it,
I'm fine, right?!
I've already got my ranger badge.
It's just for Ariane, right?!
Yeah.
However!
I'll assign you a separate
training course!
Wha?!
For you, engaging with magic is more
pertinent than training your body.
Listen up! For the Magicks War,
we need to strengthen your body first!
And there's only one important thing!
Your answer is "ranger!"
Do you understand, trainee Amelia?!
Ranger, I say!
Ranger!
Training will commence
immediately tomorrow!
Do you understand?
Ranger!
I say!
Again!
Ranger!
I mean, nooo!
Good morning, Ray.
Good morning, senpai.
You're out early again.
Because today's the day
we have our shift together.
How are you doing?
I'm doing well, thanks to you.
And I can use magic
without problems, too.
I'm very happy to hear that.
It's all thanks to the
spell you cast on me.
That reminds me.
I heard you are participating
in the Magicks War.
Yes.
I am going to form a team
with Amelia and Ariane.
Is something wrong?
You're surrounded by only women.
Really?
There are Evi and Albert,
and all the guys from the
Environmental Research Club.
Sure, but...
I'd like to be with you too.
You shouldn't push yourself right now.
I worry about you.
You do?
Yes.
I'm always thinking about you.
Ba-boom!
Oh, come on now.
Ray, you're so...
Seriously...
Ray...
Senpai?
Ray!
Amelia.
I figured I'd find you here.
Grr.
I wanted to ask you something
about my training.
Got it.
I'll meet you in the classroom,
once I'm done here.
All right, thank you.
Ahem!
Good morning, Amelia.
Kinokon!
Good morning, Rebecca-senpai.
Takepoko, takepoko.
I'll send Ray over
after the "two of us"
enjoy breakfast "alone."
I want curry!
Is that an abuse of your station?
They have hayashi rice, too!
As the president of the club?
Or...
As the president of the student council?
Oh no, no such thing is happening.
Takepoko, takepoko.
Kinokon!
What's all this pressure?
And these strange animals?
One moment.
What is this?!
Amelia.
Yes?
Can we make a deal?
A deal...?
I'm worried!
About?
About Ariane.
How so?
Her training would have her be
with Ray all day long... alone.
I suppose that's true, yes.
That's dangerous!
I'm sure she also thinks of Ray as...
N-No way!
I don't think...
Put your hand on your
heart and think about it!
I'm certain you know
what I'm talking about!
I want to keep living, next to you.
Amelia!
Get up!
Want a bite?
So, what do you say?
But I mean, still...
He's oblivious to the fact
that he's a total charmer.
We can't afford another rival
who's smitten with him.
Don't you agree?
Ray!
You got invited by Ariane, right?
Yeah.
Thinking about it,
you and her have a good vibe.
Personality-wise.
Does that mean you know her well?
I mean, we've met at noble parties.
How should I put it?
She's pretty enthusiastic!
True, she's passionate.
I mean, her soul.
I see.
I get the same feeling.
That makes sense then.
Excuse me.
Come right in, Amelia.
Rebecca.
So we're entering a non-aggression treaty
for the duration of the tournament, I see.
What's going on?
Dina.
Y-Yes.
May I ask you a favor?
Yes...
We've been waiting for you.
Evi.
Albert, you're here too.
We heard you formed a team
with Amelia and Lady Ariane?
Yeah.
I wouldn't have minded
being on a team with you.
Sorry.
No, we're actually thrilled.
We want to see what fighting you is like.
So you two...
Yeah, we formed a team.
From now on, we'll be rivals.
Teams have three people on them.
So who is your third?
That's a good question.
We don't have anyone yet...
But we know who we want.
I see.
Good luck to us all!
Yeah.
To all of us.
Oh, Ray! Did you get even taller?
I didn't, Master.
I see, I see.
So, what's up?
Right. So actually...
This is about the Magicks War.
Fast as always.
Why not?
Your overheating's gotten
pretty good right?
Yes. So then...
You're free to do as you please.
By the way...
Hello.
Ray White, it's been a while.
Lieselotte.
I was just wanting to speak with you.
I was just asking Lydia for advice.
More like forcing me to give it.
Then it's perfect timing.
Hey, don't ignore me.
Because I had something I wanted
to discuss with you, too.
A good morning to you, Amelia.
Good morning, Ariane.
Is something wrong?
Oh, nothing's wrong...
Good morning, Amelia and Ariane!
He's here!
Good morning, Ray.
That... is you, right?
Phew...
All right!
We're going to start with
a 20-kilometer run.
Are you ready?
Ranger! I say!
So that part's unchanged.
Trainee Amelia, what was that?
R-Ranger!
Ranger!
Rangfrrgb!
So this is the Ainsworth-style bootcamp.
Why do I have to do this too?
This was a demonstration before
we start our real training.
Trainee Amelia, starting next week,
you'll be on a special two-week
training program.
What's this?
You'll find out when you get there.
If you make it back alive,
your magical abilities will increase
to an even higher level.
Trainee Ariane, you will sleep
and train at my house back home.
Ranger, I say!
Now just one minute!
What is it?
I'm coming to your house too!
No, what you need to train
is your magical skills.
Besides, we will only be doing
physical training non-stop.
Ariane!
Yes?
Over here!
Ray, you stay there!
Please be gentle.
Up, up, down, down, left,
right, left, right, B.
Ray. I'll accept it for now.
All right.
Good to hear.
So, what were you two talking about?
Don't you worry about that!
Right, right.
I definitely need to keep an eye on this.
What did you say?
Starting this weekend, it seems.
I can't believe this.
He really has no self-awareness.
I hope nothing happens.
I think something might.
So you're saying it's
in the back of this?
Let's go.
You're here.
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
Let's go, Ariane!
Yes, I say!
Once we leave this place
behind, it'll be right there.
Yes, I say!
Ray, what's wrong?
Pow!
Ray!
A girl?!
I missed you, Stella!
You've grown again.
Just a little.
What about you, Big Brother?
I'm the same as always.
"Big Brother?!"
Ariane, let me introduce you.
I'm Stella White.
I'm my big brother's little sister.
Big brother!?
Little sister?!
I'm Rebecca.
~ Next Episode Preview ~
I'm Amelia.
I'm Dina.
This is the preview.
The Magicks War is coming up.
Everybody is training on their own.
In some deep deep forest!
That person shows up again!
I can't believe it!
Next time on The Iceblade
Sorcerer Shall Rule the World!
Two!
Episode 2 will be full of training and...
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
"The Boy Who Is the World's
Strongest Sorcerer Dons a Mask."
Episode 02
The Boy Who Is the
World's Strongest Sorcerer Dons a Mask
Again?!